A Guide to the Trilateral Commission (North America) records FA420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings, 1972-2001; 1; 42.06 Cubic Feet 90 letter document boxes and 6 record storage boxes
  - Principal International Meetings, 1.2
    - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1990 April
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Cheney (Box 52, Folder 569)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Israeli-Palestinian (Box 52, Folder 570)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Latin America at a Crossroads (Box 52, Folder 571)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Table of Contents (Box 52, Folder 572)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Change in Europe Discussions (Box 52, Folder 573)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files -Bouchard (Box 52, Folder 574)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Delours (Box 52, Folder 575)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Motono (Box 53, Folder 576)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Geremck (Box 53, Folder 577)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Lambsdorff (Box 53, Folder 578)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Thygesen (Box 53, Folder 579)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Watanabe (Box 53, Folder 580)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Howell (Box 53, Folder 581)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Gotlieb (Box 53, Folder 582)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Nye (Box 53, Folder 583)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Ogata (Box 53, Folder 584)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Brzezinski (Box 53, Folder 585)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Beyond Interdependence (Box 53, Folder 586)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Boskin (Box 53, Folder 587)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Bouchard (Box 53, Folder 588)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Thygesen (Box 53, Folder 589)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Feldstein (Box 53, Folder 590)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Watanabe (Box 53, Folder 591)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Morita (Box 53, Folder 592)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Bios (Box 54, Folder 593)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - NHK (Box 54, Folder 594)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 595)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Staff Program (Box 54, Folder 596)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Program (Box 54, Folder 597)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Diagrams (Box 54, Folder 598)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Press (Box 54, Folder 599)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Place Cards (Box 54, Folder 600)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Photographer (Box 54, Folder 601)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Interpreters (Box 54, Folder 602)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Andrew Frankel Files - Audio/Visual (Box 54, Folder 603)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files (Box 54, Folder 604)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - General (Box 54, Folder 604A)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Passports and Security (Box 55, Folder 605)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Spouses Program (Box 55, Folder 606)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Possible Dinner Sites (Box 55, Folder 607)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Meeting and Trip/Future Trips (Box 55, Folder 608)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Planning Meeting, 1990 January19 (Box 55, Folder 609)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Hotel (Box 55, Folder 610)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - DC Trip - Scoweroff Dinner, 1990 April 27 (Box 55, Folder 611)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Design (Box 55, Folder 612)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - RSVP (Box 55, Folder 613)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Originals (Box 55, Folder 614)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Press (Box 55, Folder 615)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Pre Plenary, Mexico City, 1990 April 18-20 (Box 55, Folder 616)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Park Hyatt, 1990 April 21-23 (Box 55, Folder 617)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Washington, 1989 August 24 (Box 55, Folder 618)
    - Plenary Meeting, Lisbon, 1992 April
      - Plenary Meeting, Lisbon - Christina Hanophy Files (Box 55, Folder 619)
      - Plenary Meeting, Lisbon - Christina Hanophy Files - Hotel and Travel Arrangements (Box 56, Folder 620)
      - Plenary Meeting, Lisbon - Christina Hanophy Files - Meeting Materials (Box 56, Folder 620A)
    - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1993 March
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Meeting, Hotel and Travel Arrangements (Box 56, Folder 621)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - General (Box 56, Folder 622)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Christina Hanophy Files - Melrose Catering (Box 56, Folder 623)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Spouses Program, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 624)
    - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo, 1994 April
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files (Box 57, Folder 625)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files - Bills/Reimbursements (Box 57, Folder 626)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files - Memoranda (Box 57, Folder 627)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files - Regrets (Box 57, Folder 628)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files - Hotel Expenses and Arrangements (Box 57, Folder 629)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files - Acceptances (Box 57, Folder 630)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Christina Hanophy Files - Spouses Program (Box 57, Folder 631)
    - Annual Meeting Publication (Tokyo), 1994
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Yaun Ming, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 632)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Zhou Xiaochuan, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 633)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Chen Qimao, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 634)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Corrigan, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 635)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Lelloouche, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 636)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Shigeki Hakamada, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 637)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Narongchai Akrasanee, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 638)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Karaganov, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 639)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Lee Hongkoo, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 640)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Miyazaki, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 641)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Motoo Shina, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 642)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Hata, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 643)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Kobayashi, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 644)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Einhorn, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 645)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Ogata, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 646)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Ruggiero, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 647)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Bergsten, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 648)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Ferrer, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 649)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Nukazawa, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 650)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Chan Heng Chee, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 651)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Graham, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 652)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Owada, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 653)
      - Annual Meeting, Tokyo - Martin Bangemann, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 654)
    - Plenary Meeting, Copenhagen, 1995 April
      - Plenary Meeting, Copenhagen - Christina Hanophy Files - Hotel Expenses (Box 58, Folder 655)
      - Plenary Meeting, Copenhagen - Christina Hanophy Files - Spouses Program (Box 58, Folder 656)
      - Plenary Meeting, Copenhagen - Christina Hanophy Files - No Copenhagen Acceptance (Box 58, Folder 657)
      - Plenary Meeting, Copenhagen - Christina Hanophy Files - Telefaxes Sent (Box 58, Folder 658)
      - Plenary Meeting, Copenhagen - Christina Hanophy Files - General (Box 58, Folder 658A)
    - Annual Meeting Publication (Copenhagen), 1995
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - E, Gerald Corrigan (Box 58, Folder 659)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Bodil Nyboe Andersen (Box 58, Folder 660)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Davignon (Box 58, Folder 661)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Feldstein (Box 58, Folder 662)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Kjell-Olok Feldt (Box 58, Folder 663)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Gustav Hagglund (Box 58, Folder 664)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Foley (Box 58, Folder 665)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Josef Joffe (Box 58, Folder 666)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Kozyrev (Box 59, Folder 667)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Willoch (Box 59, Folder 668)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Seidenfaden (Box 59, Folder 669)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Sutherland (Box 59, Folder 670)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Svanholm (Box 59, Folder 671)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Tarasyuk (Box 59, Folder 672)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Onyszkiewicz (Box 59, Folder 673)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Rasmussen (Box 59, Folder 674)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Roth (Box 59, Folder 675)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Jorg Schonbohm (Box 59, Folder 676)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - James Steinberg (Box 59, Folder 677)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Lambsdorff (Box 59, Folder 678)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Lennart Meri (Box 59, Folder 679)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Murofushi (Box 59, Folder 680)
      - Annual Meeting, Copenhagen - Koji Watanabe (Box 59, Folder 681)
    - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver, 1996 April
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Christina Hanophy Files - No Acceptance (Box 59, Folder 682)
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Christina Hanophy Files - Vancouver Trip (Box 59, Folder 683)
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files (Box 59, Folder 684)
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Christina Hanophy Files - Waterfront Hotel (Box 60, Folder 685)
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Christina Hanophy Files - Maureen Chant (Box 60, Folder 686)
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Christina Hanophy Files (Box 60, Folder 687)
      - Plenary Meeting, Vancouver - Christina Hanophy Files (Box 60, Folder 688)
    - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo, 1997 March
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Yuan Ming (Box 61, Folder 689)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Publication (Box 61, Folder 690)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Publication (Box 61, Folder 691)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Publication (Box 61, Folder 692)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Publication (Box 61, Folder 693)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Publication (Box 61, Folder 694)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Anand Panyarachun (Box 61, Folder 695)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Wanandi (Box 61, Folder 696)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Ikeda (Box 61, Folder 697)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Winston Lord (Box 61, Folder 698)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Ronnie Chan (Box 61, Folder 699)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Estanisklao (Box 61, Folder 700)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Ross Garaut (Box 61, Folder 701)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Zhu (Box 61, Folder 702)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Bios (Box 61, Folder 703)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - New Info (Badges, Name) (Box 61, Folder 704)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - European Badge Spares (Box 61, Folder 705)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - North American Badge Spares (Box 61, Folder 706)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Japanese Badge Spares (Box 61, Folder 707)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Ruggiero (Box 62, Folder 708)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Kato (Box 62, Folder 709)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Hachimoto (Box 62, Folder 710)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Gyohten (Box 62, Folder 711)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Sakurai (Box 62, Folder 712)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Biedenkopf (Box 62, Folder 713)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Ruding (Box 62, Folder 714)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Sirkka Hamalainen (Box 62, Folder 715)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Nye (Box 62, Folder 716)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - House (Box 62, Folder 717)
      - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Foley (Box 62, Folder 718)
    - Plenary Meeting, Berlin, 1998 March
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Other Berlin Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 719)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Program (Box 62, Folder 720)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Other Berlin Background Papers (Box 62, Folder 721)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Section 1 (Box 62, Folder 722)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Section 2 (Box 62, Folder 723)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Section 3 (Box 62, Folder 724)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Section 4 (Box 62, Folder 725)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Section 5 (Box 62, Folder 726)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Section 6 (Box 62, Folder 727)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Miyazawa (Box 62, Folder 728)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Wolf (Box 62, Folder 729)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Fisher (Box 62, Folder 730)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Fung (Box 62, Folder 731)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Wanandi (Box 62, Folder 732)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files (Box 63, Folder 733)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Berlin Texts (Box 63, Folder 734)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - North American Bios (Box 63, Folder 735)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - European Bios (Box 63, Folder 736)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Japanese Bios (Box 63, Folder 737)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Narongchai Akrasanee (Box 64, Folder 738)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Middle East Excerpts (Box 64, Folder 738A)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Holbrooke (Box 64, Folder 738B)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Ellemann-Jensen (Box 64, Folder 738C)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Rockefeller, David (Box 64, Folder 739)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Dini (Box 64, Folder 739A)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Solana (Box 64, Folder 739B)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Han Sung-Joo (Box 64, Folder 739C)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Kissinger (Box 64, Folder 740)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Kusukawa (Box 64, Folder 740A)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Kwasniewski (Box 64, Folder 740B)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Yavlinsky (Box 64, Folder 740C)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Karaganov (Box 64, Folder 741)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Herzog (Box 64, Folder 741A)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Baring (Box 64, Folder 741B)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Verheugen (Box 64, Folder 741C)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Schauble (Box 64, Folder 742)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Kohl (Box 64, Folder 743)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - von Prierer (Box 64, Folder 744)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Program (Box 64, Folder 745)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Charles B. Heck, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 746)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Charles B. Heck, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 747)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Charles B. Heck, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 748)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Christina Hanophy, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 749)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Christina Hanophy - Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 750)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Christina Hanophy - Arrangements (Box 65, Folder 751)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Christina Hanophy - Hotel and Travel Arrangements (Box 65, Folder 752)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Charles B. Heck, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 753)
      - Plenary Meeting, Berlin - Hanophy - Preliminary Questionaires (Box 66, Folder 754)
    - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1999 March
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Spouses Program (Box 66, Folder 755)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files, 1999 March 13-15 (Box 66, Folder 756)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files, 1999 March (Box 66, Folder 757)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Master Euros (Box 66, Folder 758)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Bios (Box 66, Folder 759)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Special Thanks (Box 66, Folder 760)
      - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Spouse Program (Box 66, Folder 761)
    - Meetings Outside the Trilateral Area
      - Meeting, Moscow (Aborted), 1980
        - Meeting, Moscow, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 762)
        - Proposed Moscow Meeting (GSF Desk File) (Box 67, Folder 763)
        - Proposed Moscow Meeting (Box 67, Folder 764)
      - Soviet-Trilateral Conference, 1982 May 5-6 (Box 67, Folder 764A)
    - Meeting, China, 1981
      - Meeting, China - George S. Franklin Desk File, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 765)
      - Proposed Peking Meeting - Background Material, 1981 May (Box 67, Folder 766)
      - Meeting, China - Xie Li & Company come to the Big Apple (Box 67, Folder 767)
      - Meeting, China - Tadashi's Notes on the Deng Meeting (Box 67, Folder 768)
      - Meeting, China - MacLaury and Rockefeller Speeches in China, 1981 May 21 (Box 67, Folder 769)
      - Meeting, China - Beijing, 1981 May 20-23 (Box 67, Folder 770)
      - Meeting, China, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 771)
      - Washington Visits - Re: China Meeting, 1981 May 11 (Box 68, Folder 772)
      - Washington Visits - Re: China Meeting, 1981 May 11 (Box 68, Folder 772A)
      - Meeting, China - Translations (Box 68, Folder 773)
      - Meeting, China - Post Meeting File (Box 68, Folder 774)
      - Meeting, China, 1981 May 20-23 (Box 68, Folder 775)
      - Meeting, China, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 776)
      - Meeting, China, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 777)
      - Meeting, China - Peking's Interpretation (Box 69, Folder 778)
      - Meeting, China - Peking: Delegations, Questionnaire, etc. (Box 69, Folder 779)
      - Meeting, China - Peking: General Correspondence, Japanese Preliminary Trip, 1980 May (Box 69, Folder 780)
      - Meeting, China (Box 69, Folder 781)
      - Meeting, China (Box 69, Folder 782)
    - Meeting, Mexico City (Aborted), 1984
      - Meeting, Mexico (Box 69, Folder 783)
      - Meeting, Mexico City, 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 784)
    - Pre-Plenary Meeting, Mexico City, 1990
      - Meeting, Mexico, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 785)
  - Other Meetings, 1.3
    Includes: Chairmen's Meetings, Three-Region Executive Committee Meetings, North American Executive Committee/Trustees Meetings, North American Events, European Group Meetings.
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1974 October (Box 70, Folder 786)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1974 October 6-7 (Box 70, Folder 787)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1974 December (Box 70, Folder 788)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1974 December 8-11 (Box 70, Folder 789)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Copenhagen, 1975 March 7-9 (Box 70, Folder 790)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Tokyo, 1975 May 25 (Box 70, Folder 791)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1976 March (Box 70, Folder 792)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Ottawa, 1976 May (Box 70, Folder 793)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Washington, D.C., 1976 May 13 (Box 70, Folder 794)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Ottawa, 1976 May (Box 70, Folder 795)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Rome, 1976 September (Box 70, Folder 796)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Rome - Program Advisory Board, 1976 September 23 (Box 70, Folder 797)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Rome, 1976 September (Box 70, Folder 798)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Rome, 1976 September 24-25 (Box 70, Folder 799)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Rome - Letter to N.A. (Box 70, Folder 800)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Tokyo, 1977 January (Box 71, Folder 801)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1977 June 17-18 (Box 71, Folder 802)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1977 June 16-18 (Box 71, Folder 803)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Washington, D.C., 1977 June (Box 71, Folder 804)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Japan, 1978 January 29-30 (Box 71, Folder 805)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1978 June 10; June 14 1978 (Box 71, Folder 806)
    - Chairmen's Recommendations on the Future of the Commission, 1978 June 14 (Box 71, Folder 807)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Tokyo, 1979 April 24 (Box 71, Folder 808)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1979 April (Box 71, Folder 809)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Canada, 1979 October 10 (Box 71, Folder 810)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1979 October (Box 71, Folder 811)
    - Chairmen's Meetings - Breakfast (7:30AM), 1980 March 23 (Box 71, Folder 812)
    - Chairmen's Meeting - Possible, 1980 September (Box 71, Folder 813)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Tokyo, 1980 September (Box 71, Folder 814)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Tokyo, 1980 September (Box 71, Folder 815)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, Tokyo, September 14-15, 1980 and Discussions in China, September 17-20, 1980, 1980 September 14-15 (Box 71, Folder 816)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Washington, March 30 and April 1, 1981 and Sharp's Meeting Notes, 1981 March 30 (Box 71, Folder 817)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Washington, 1981 April (Box 72, Folder 818)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1981 March-April (Box 72, Folder 819)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Paris, 1981 November 13-14 (Box 72, Folder 820)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Paris, 1981 November 13-14 (Box 72, Folder 821)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1981 November 8-14 (Box 72, Folder 822)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, Paris, 1981 November (Box 72, Folder 823)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, New York, 1982 November (Box 72, Folder 824)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, New York, 1982 November (Box 72, Folder 825)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, New York, 1982 November (Box 72, Folder 826)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 827)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, Tokyo, 1983 November (Box 72, Folder 828)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1983 November (Box 72, Folder 829)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 830)
    - Chairmen's Meetings, Paris, 1984 November 15 (Box 72, Folder 831)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1985 November (Box 73, Folder 832)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1985 November (Box 73, Folder 833)
    - Chairmen's Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1985 November (Box 73, Folder 834)